Guide to the New York University Collection of Papyri, Ostraka, and Cuneiform Tablets MSS.559
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I. Papyri Fragments, 55 Linear Feet in 44 small flat boxes and 2 oversize flat boxes
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0623, cuid31424; 1 fragment 09.6 x 06.5 cm (Box 17, Item P.NYU inv 0623)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 053
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0624, cuid31425; 1 fragment 09.0 x 07.0 cm (Box 17, Item P.NYU inv 0624)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 054
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0625, cuid31426; 1 fragment 02.5 x 03.0 cm (Box 17, Item P.NYU inv 0625)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 055
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0626, cuid31427; 1 fragment 06.0 x 05.0 cm (Box 17, Item P.NYU inv 0626)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 056
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0627, cuid31428; 1 fragment 02.5 x 07.5 cm (Box 17, Item P.NYU inv 0627)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 057
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0628, cuid31429; 1 fragment 05.5 x 12.0 cm (Box 17, Item P.NYU inv 0628)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 058
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0629, cuid31430; 1 fragment 09.0 x 06.5 cm (Box 17, Item P.NYU inv 0629)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 059
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0630, cuid31431; 1 fragment 15.0 x 10.5 cm (Box 17, Item P.NYU inv 0630)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 060
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0631, cuid31432; 1 fragment 05.5 x 04.0 cm (Box 17, Item P.NYU inv 0631)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 061
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0632, cuid31433; 1 fragment 05.0 x 06.0 cm (Box 17, Item P.NYU inv 0632)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 062
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0633, cuid31434; 1 fragment 02.5 x 03.5 cm (Box 17, Item P.NYU inv 0633)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 063
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0634, cuid31435; 1 fragment 11.5 x 06.0 cm (Box 17, Item P.NYU inv 0634)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 064
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0635, cuid31436; 1 fragment 07.0 x 03.5 cm (Box 17, Item P.NYU inv 0635)
    APIS Number: NYU.inv.cairo 065
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0636, cuid31437; 1 fragment 09.0 x 10.0 cm (Box 17, Item P.NYU inv 0636)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 066
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0637, cuid31438; 1 fragment 03.0 x 02.5 cm (Box 17, Item P.NYU inv 0637)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 067
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0638, cuid31439; 1 fragment 10.5 x 08.0 cm (Box 17, Item P.NYU inv 0638)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 068
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0639, cuid31440; 1 fragment 12.0 x 09.5 cm (Box 17, Item P.NYU inv 0639)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 069
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0640, cuid31441; 1 fragment 07.5 x 08.5 cm (Box 17, Item P.NYU inv 0640)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 070
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0641, cuid31442; 1 fragment 03.0 x 11.0 cm (Box 17, Item P.NYU inv 0641)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 071
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0642, cuid31443; 1 fragment 05.0 x 07.0 cm (Box 17, Item P.NYU inv 0642)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 072
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0643, cuid31444; 1 fragment 08.0 x 11.0 cm (Box 17, Item P.NYU inv 0643)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 073
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0644, cuid31445; 1 fragment 02.5 x 06.0 cm (Box 17, Item P.NYU inv 0644)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 074
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0645, cuid31446; 1 fragment 03.5 x 06.0 cm (Box 17, Item P.NYU inv 0645)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 075
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0646, cuid31447; 1 fragment 04.5 x 06.0 cm (Box 17, Item P.NYU inv 0646)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 076
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0647, cuid31448; 1 fragment 06.0 x 05.5 cm (Box 17, Item P.NYU inv 0647)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 077
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0648, cuid31449; 1 fragment 04.0 x 09.5 cm (Box 17, Item P.NYU inv 0648)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 078
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0649, cuid31450; 1 fragment 11.5 x 10.5 cm (Box 17, Item P.NYU inv 0649)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 079
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0650, cuid31451; 1 fragment 04.0 x 03.0 cm (Box 17, Item P.NYU inv 0650)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 080
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0651, cuid31452; 1 fragment 04.5 x 09.0 cm (Box 17, Item P.NYU inv 0651)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 081
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0652, cuid31453; 1 fragment 14.5 x 06.5 cm (Box 17, Item P.NYU inv 0652)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 082
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0653, cuid31454; 1 fragment 07.5 x 03.0 cm (Box 17, Item P.NYU inv 0653)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 083
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0654.01, cuid31455; 1 fragment 06.0 x 07.5 cm (Box 17, Item P.NYU inv 0654.01)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 084.01
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0654.02, cuid31456; 1 fragment 11.0 x 12.0 cm (Box 17, Item P.NYU inv 0654.02)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 084.02
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0655, cuid31457; 1 fragment 05.0 x 08.0 cm (Box 17, Item P.NYU inv 0655)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 085
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0656, cuid31458; 1 fragment 02.5 x 05.0 cm (Box 17, Item P.NYU inv 0656)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 086
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0657, cuid31459; 1 fragment 03.5 x 08.0 cm (Box 17, Item P.NYU inv 0657)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 087
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0658, cuid31460; 1 fragment 03.5 x 04.0 cm (Box 17, Item P.NYU inv 0658)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 088
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0659, cuid31461; 1 fragment 07.5 x 07.5 cm (Box 17, Item P.NYU inv 0659)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 089
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0660, cuid31462; 1 fragment 05.5 x 05.0 cm (Box 17, Item P.NYU inv 0660)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 090
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0661, cuid31463; 1 fragment 04.0 x 03.0 cm (Box 17, Item P.NYU inv 0661)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 091
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0662, cuid31464; 1 fragment 06.5 x 03.5 cm (Box 17, Item P.NYU inv 0662)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 092
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0663, cuid31465; 1 fragment 14.0 x 06.0 cm (Box 17, Item P.NYU inv 0663)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 093
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0664, cuid31466; 1 fragment 05.0 x 11.5 cm (Box 18, Item P.NYU inv 0664)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 094
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0665, cuid31467; 1 fragment 20.5 x 07.0 cm (Box 18, Item P.NYU inv 0665)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 095
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0666, cuid31468; 1 fragment 05.0 x 04.0 cm (Box 18, Item P.NYU inv 0666)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 096
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0667, cuid31469; 1 fragment 01.5 x 04.0 cm (Box 18, Item P.NYU inv 0667)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 097
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0668, cuid31470; 1 fragment 02.5 x 04.5 cm (Box 18, Item P.NYU inv 0668)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 098
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0669, cuid31471; 1 fragment 04.0 x 03.5 cm (Box 18, Item P.NYU inv 0669)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 099
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0670, cuid31472; 1 fragment 05.0 x 04.5 cm (Box 18, Item P.NYU inv 0670)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 100
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0671, cuid31473; 1 fragment 11.0 x 04.0 cm (Box 18, Item P.NYU inv 0671)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 101
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0672, cuid31474; 1 fragment 07.0 x 06.0 cm (Box 18, Item P.NYU inv 0672)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 102
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0673, cuid31475; 1 fragment 20.0 x 12.0 cm (Box 40, Item P.NYU inv 0673)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 103
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0674, cuid31476; 1 fragment 07.5 x 03.5 cm (Box 18, Item P.NYU inv 0674)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 104
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0675, cuid31477; 1 fragment 06.5 x 03.0 cm (Box 18, Item P.NYU inv 0675)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 105
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0676, cuid31478; 1 fragment 05.5 x 09.0 cm (Box 18, Item P.NYU inv 0676)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 106
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0677, cuid31479; 1 fragment 08.5 x 08.0 cm (Box 18, Item P.NYU inv 0677)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 107
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0678.01, cuid31480; 1 fragment 21.5 x 21.5 cm (Box 40, Item P.NYU inv 0678.01)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 108.01
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0678.02, cuid31481; 1 fragment 02.5 x 01.0 cm (Box 40, Item P.NYU inv 0678.02)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 108.02
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0679, cuid31482; 1 fragment 08.0 x 15.0 cm (Box 18, Item P.NYU inv 0679)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 109
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0680, cuid31483; 1 fragment 10.0 x 05.5 cm (Box 18, Item P.NYU inv 0680)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 110
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0681, cuid31484; 1 fragment 10.5 x 06.5 cm (Box 18, Item P.NYU inv 0681)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 111
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0682, cuid31485; 1 fragment 06.0 x 08.5 cm (Box 18, Item P.NYU inv 0682)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 112
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0683, cuid31486; 1 fragment 05.5 x 13.0 cm (Box 18, Item P.NYU inv 0683)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 113
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0684, cuid31487; 1 fragment 06.5 x 06.5 cm (Box 18, Item P.NYU inv 0684)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 114
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0685, cuid31488; 1 fragment 02.0 x 05.5 cm (Box 18, Item P.NYU inv 0685)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 115
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0686, cuid31489; 1 fragment 01.5 x 04.0 cm (Box 18, Item P.NYU inv 0686)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 116
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0687, cuid31490; 1 fragment 04.0 x 11.0 cm (Box 18, Item P.NYU inv 0687)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 117
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0688, cuid31491; 1 fragment 12.0 x 07.5 cm (Box 18, Item P.NYU inv 0688)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 118
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0689, cuid31492; 1 fragment 05.5 x 06.0 cm (Box 18, Item P.NYU inv 0689)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 119
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0690, cuid31493; 1 fragment 10.0 x 06.0 cm (Box 18, Item P.NYU inv 0690)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 120
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0691, cuid31494; 1 fragment 05.0 x 05.0 cm (Box 18, Item P.NYU inv 0691)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 121
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0692, cuid31495; 1 fragment 14.0 x 06.0 cm (Box 18, Item P.NYU inv 0692)
    APIS Number: NYU inv.cairo 122
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0693, cuid31496; 1 fragment 13.0 x 10.0 cm (Box 18, Item P.NYU inv 0693)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0694, cuid31497; 1 fragment 10.0 x 04.5 cm (Box 18, Item P.NYU inv 0694)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0695.01, cuid31498; 1 fragment 02.5 x 12.5 cm (Box 18, Item P.NYU inv 0695.01)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0695.02, cuid31499; 1 fragment 02.5 x 05.0 cm (Box 18, Item P.NYU inv 0695.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0696, cuid31500; 1 fragment 10.0 x 06.5 cm (Box 18, Item P.NYU inv 0696)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0697, cuid31501; 1 fragment 09.5 x 06.5 cm (Box 18, Item P.NYU inv 0697)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0698, cuid31502; 1 fragment 06.0 x 06.0 cm (Box 18, Item P.NYU inv 0698)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0699, cuid31503; 1 fragment 06.0 x 09.5 cm (Box 18, Item P.NYU inv 0699)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0700, cuid31504; 1 fragment 05.5 x 06.0 cm (Box 18, Item P.NYU inv 0700)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0701, cuid31505; 1 fragment 13.0 x 07.0 cm (Box 18, Item P.NYU inv 0701)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0702, cuid31506; 1 fragment 11.0 x 06.0 cm (Box 18, Item P.NYU inv 0702)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0703.01, cuid31507; 1 fragment 03.0 x 02.0 cm (Box 18, Item P.NYU inv 0703.01)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0703.02, cuid31508; 1 fragment 07.5 x 06.0 cm (Box 18, Item P.NYU inv 0703.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0703.03, cuid31509; 1 fragment 01.0 x 01.0 cm (Box 18, Item P.NYU inv 0703.03)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0704, cuid31510; 1 fragment 20.0 x 11.5 cm (Box 18, Item P.NYU inv 0704)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0705.01, cuid31511; 1 fragment 06.5 x 15.5 cm (Box 18, Item P.NYU inv 0705.01)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0705.02, cuid31512; 1 fragment 02.0 x 02.0 cm (Box 18, Item P.NYU inv 0705.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0706, cuid31513; 1 fragment 12.0 x 17.0 cm (Box 18, Item P.NYU inv 0706)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0707, cuid31514; 1 fragment 12.0 x 13.5 cm (Box 18, Item P.NYU inv 0707)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0708, cuid31515; 1 fragment 06.0 x 10.0 cm (Box 18, Item P.NYU inv 0708)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0709, cuid31516; 1 fragment 21.0 x 13.5 cm (Box 40, Item P.NYU inv 0709)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0710, cuid31517; 1 fragment 09.0 x 04.0 cm (Box 18, Item P.NYU inv 0710)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0711, cuid31518; 1 fragment 18.0 x 12.5 cm (Box 18, Item P.NYU inv 0711)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0712, cuid31519; 1 fragment 10.0 x 11.5 cm (Box 18, Item P.NYU inv 0712)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0713, cuid31520; 1 fragment 05.5 x 08.0 cm (Box 18, Item P.NYU inv 0713)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0714, cuid31521; 1 fragment 11.5 x 06.0 cm (Box 18, Item P.NYU inv 0714)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0715, cuid31522; 1 fragment 07.0 x 05.5 cm (Box 18, Item P.NYU inv 0715)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0716, cuid31523; 1 fragment 05.0 x 05.0 cm (Box 18, Item P.NYU inv 0716)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0717, cuid31524; 1 fragment 07.0 x 14.0 cm (Box 18, Item P.NYU inv 0717)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0718, cuid31525; 1 fragment 13.5 x 07.5 cm (Box 18, Item P.NYU inv 0718)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0719.01, cuid31526; 1 fragment 05.0 x 03.0 cm (Box 42, Item P.NYU inv 0719.01)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0719.02, cuid31527; 1 fragment 03.5 x 02.0 cm (Box 42, Item P.NYU inv 0719.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0720.01, cuid31528; 1 fragment 04.0 x 03.0 cm (Box 42, Item P.NYU inv 0720.01)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0720.02, cuid31529; 1 fragment 04.0 x 03.0 cm (Box 42, Item P.NYU inv 0720.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0720.03, cuid31530; 1 fragment 04.0 x 03.0 cm (Box 42, Item P.NYU inv 0720.03)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0721.01, cuid31531; 1 fragment 26.0 x 10.5 cm (Box 40, Item P.NYU inv 0721.01)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0721.02, cuid31532; 1 fragment 09.0 x 06.0 cm (Box 40, Item P.NYU inv 0721.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0722.01, cuid31533; 8 fragments 07.0 x 05.0 cm (Box 18, Item P.NYU inv 0722.01)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0722.02, cuid31534; 8 fragments 09.0 x 07.0 cm (Box 18, Item P.NYU inv 0722.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0722.03, cuid31535; 8 fragments 09.0 x 07.5 cm (Box 18, Item P.NYU inv 0722.03)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0722.04, cuid31536; 8 fragments 03.5 x 02.0 cm (Box 18, Item P.NYU inv 0722.04)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0722.05, cuid31537; 8 fragments 04.0 x 04.0 cm (Box 18, Item P.NYU inv 0722.05)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0722.06, cuid31538; 8 fragments 04.5 x 03.0 cm (Box 19, Item P.NYU inv 0722.06)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0722.07, cuid31539; 8 fragments 06.5 x 05.0 cm (Box 19, Item P.NYU inv 0722.07)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0722.08, cuid31540; 8 fragments 10.0 x 02.5 cm (Box 19, Item P.NYU inv 0722.08)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0723, cuid31541; 1 fragment 12.0 x 10.0 cm (Box 19, Item P.NYU inv 0723)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0724, cuid31542; 1 fragment 07.5 x 03.0 cm (Box 19, Item P.NYU inv 0724)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0725, cuid31543; 1 fragment 06.0 x 04.0 cm (Box 19, Item P.NYU inv 0725)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0726, cuid31544; 1 fragment 07.5 x 06.5 cm (Box 19, Item P.NYU inv 0726)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0727, cuid31545; 1 fragment 07.0 x 14.0 cm (Box 19, Item P.NYU inv 0727)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0728, cuid31546; 1 fragment 09.0 x 06.0 cm (Box 19, Item P.NYU inv 0728)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0729, cuid31547; 1 fragment 08.0 x 14.5 cm (Box 19, Item P.NYU inv 0729)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0730, cuid31548; 1 fragment 03.0 x 08.0 cm (Box 19, Item P.NYU inv 0730)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0731, cuid31549; 1 fragment 09.0 x 13.5 cm (Box 19, Item P.NYU inv 0731)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0732, cuid31550; 1 fragment 12.5 x 09.0 cm (Box 19, Item P.NYU inv 0732)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0733, cuid31551; 1 fragment 11.5 x 09.0 cm (Box 19, Item P.NYU inv 0733)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0734, cuid31552; 1 fragment 18.0 x 05.0 cm (Box 19, Item P.NYU inv 0734)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0735, cuid31553; 1 fragment 18.0 x 07.0 cm (Box 19, Item P.NYU inv 0735)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0736, cuid31554; 1 fragment 13.0 x 12.0 cm (Box 19, Item P.NYU inv 0736)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0737.01, cuid31555; 1 fragment 07.0 x 02.0 cm (Box 19, Item P.NYU inv 0737.01)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0737.02, cuid31556; 1 fragment 10.0 x 04.0 cm (Box 19, Item P.NYU inv 0737.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0738, cuid31557; 1 fragment 10.0 x 06.0 cm (Box 19, Item P.NYU inv 0738)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0739, cuid31558; 1 fragment 06.5 x 11.5 cm (Box 19, Item P.NYU inv 0739)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0740, cuid31559; 1 fragment 05.0 x 10.0 cm (Box 19, Item P.NYU inv 0740)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0741, cuid31560; 1 fragment 12.0 x 04.5 cm (Box 19, Item P.NYU inv 0741)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0742, cuid31561; 1 fragment 19.5 x 08.5 cm (Box 19, Item P.NYU inv 0742)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0743, cuid31562; 1 fragment 16.0 x 09.5 cm (Box 19, Item P.NYU inv 0743)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0744.01, cuid31563; 1 fragment 09.0 x 19.5 cm (Box 19, Item P.NYU inv 0744.01)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0744.02, cuid31564; 1 fragment 00.5 x 02.2 cm (Box 19, Item P.NYU inv 0744.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0745, cuid31565; 1 fragment 03.5 x 04.0 cm (Box 19, Item P.NYU inv 0745)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0746, cuid31566; 1 fragment 12.0 x 10.5 cm (Box 19, Item P.NYU inv 0746)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0747, cuid31567; 1 fragment 06.5 x 07.0 cm (Box 19, Item P.NYU inv 0747)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0748, cuid31568; 1 fragment 14.0 x 05.5 cm (Box 19, Item P.NYU inv 0748)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0749.01, cuid31569; 1 fragment 13.0 x 14.0 cm (Box 19, Item P.NYU inv 0749.01)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0749.02, cuid31570; 1 fragment 04.0 x 07.5 cm (Box 19, Item P.NYU inv 0749.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0749.03, cuid31571; 1 fragment 02.5 x 02.5 cm (Box 19, Item P.NYU inv 0749.03)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0750, cuid31572; 1 fragment 08.0 x 10.0 cm (Box 19, Item P.NYU inv 0750)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0751, cuid31573; 1 fragment 02.5 x 02.5 cm (Box 19, Item P.NYU inv 0751)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0752, cuid31574; 1 fragment 21.0 x 08.0 cm (Box 19, Item P.NYU inv 0752)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0753, cuid31575; 1 fragment 03.5 x 12.0 cm (Box 19, Item P.NYU inv 0753)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0754, cuid31576; 1 fragment 09.0 x 06.0 cm (Box 19, Item P.NYU inv 0754)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0755, cuid31577; 1 fragment 08.0 x 13.0 cm (Box 19, Item P.NYU inv 0755)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0756, cuid31578; 1 fragment 02.5 x 04.5 cm (Box 19, Item P.NYU inv 0756)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0757, cuid31579; 1 fragment 01.5 x 04.0 cm (Box 19, Item P.NYU inv 0757)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0758, cuid31580; 1 fragment 04.0 x 06.0 cm (Box 19, Item P.NYU inv 0758)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0759, cuid31581; 1 fragment 04.5 x 08.5 cm (Box 19, Item P.NYU inv 0759)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0760, cuid31582; 1 fragment 04.0 x 07.0 cm (Box 19, Item P.NYU inv 0760)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0761, cuid31583; 1 fragment 09.0 x 03.5 cm (Box 19, Item P.NYU inv 0761)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0762, cuid31584; 1 fragment 08.0 x 05.0 cm (Box 19, Item P.NYU inv 0762)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0764, cuid31585; 1 fragment 05.5 x 05.5 cm (Box 19, Item P.NYU inv 0764)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0765, cuid31586; 1 fragment 05.0 x 07.0 cm (Box 19, Item P.NYU inv 0765)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0766, cuid31587; 1 fragment 01.5 x 05.5 cm (Box 19, Item P.NYU inv 0766)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0767, cuid31588; 1 fragment 04.5 x 04.0 cm (Box 19, Item P.NYU inv 0767)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0768, cuid31589; 1 fragment 04.0 x 02.5 cm (Box 19, Item P.NYU inv 0768)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0769, cuid31590; 1 fragment 07.5 x 11.0 cm (Box 19, Item P.NYU inv 0769)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0770, cuid31591; 1 fragment 05.5 x 04.5 cm (Box 19, Item P.NYU inv 0770)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0772, cuid31592; 1 fragment 06.5 x 07.5 cm (Box 19, Item P.NYU inv 0772)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0773, cuid31593; 1 fragment 02.0 x 03.0 cm (Box 19, Item P.NYU inv 0773)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0774, cuid31594; 1 fragment 07.0 x 06.0 cm (Box 19, Item P.NYU inv 0774)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0775, cuid31595; 1 fragment 07.0 x 05.0 cm (Box 19, Item P.NYU inv 0775)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0776, cuid31596; 1 fragment 07.5 x 04.0 cm (Box 19, Item P.NYU inv 0776)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0777, cuid31597; 1 fragment 02.0 x 03.0 cm (Box 19, Item P.NYU inv 0777)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0778, cuid31598; 1 fragment 02.0 x 07.5 cm (Box 19, Item P.NYU inv 0778)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0779, cuid31599; 1 fragment 06.0 x 03.0 cm (Box 19, Item P.NYU inv 0779)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0780, cuid31600; 1 fragment 06.5 x 02.5 cm (Box 19, Item P.NYU inv 0780)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0781, cuid31601; 1 fragment 05.5 x 04.0 cm (Box 19, Item P.NYU inv 0781)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0782, cuid31602; 1 fragment 08.5 x 16.0 cm (Box 20, Item P.NYU inv 0782)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0783, cuid31603; 1 fragment 03.0 x 03.0 cm (Box 20, Item P.NYU inv 0783)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0784, cuid31604; 1 fragment 06.0 x 15.0 cm (Box 20, Item P.NYU inv 0784)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0785.01, cuid31605; 1 fragment 08.5 x 05.5 cm (Box 20, Item P.NYU inv 0785.01)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0785.02, cuid31606; 1 fragment 03.5 x 08.5 cm (Box 20, Item P.NYU inv 0785.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0786, cuid31607; 1 fragment 04.5 x 03.0 cm (Box 20, Item P.NYU inv 0786)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0787, cuid31608; 1 fragment 05.0 x 02.5 cm (Box 20, Item P.NYU inv 0787)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0788, cuid31609; 1 fragment 03.0 x 02.5 cm (Box 20, Item P.NYU inv 0788)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0789, cuid31610; 1 fragment 02.5 x 04.0 cm (Box 20, Item P.NYU inv 0789)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0790, cuid31611; 1 fragment 06.5 x 05.0 cm (Box 20, Item P.NYU inv 0790)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0791, cuid31612; 1 fragment 03.0 x 03.5 cm (Box 20, Item P.NYU inv 0791)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0792, cuid31613; 1 fragment 01.5 x 01.5 cm (Box 20, Item P.NYU inv 0792)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0793, cuid31614; 1 fragment 02.0 x 02.0 cm (Box 20, Item P.NYU inv 0793)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0794, cuid31615; 1 fragment 01.5 x 02.5 cm (Box 20, Item P.NYU inv 0794)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0795, cuid31616; 1 fragment 08.5 x 07.5 cm (Box 20, Item P.NYU inv 0795)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0796, cuid31617; 1 fragment 08.5 x 05.5 cm (Box 20, Item P.NYU inv 0796)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0797, cuid31618; 1 fragment 02.0 x 01.5 cm (Box 20, Item P.NYU inv 0797)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0798, cuid31619; 1 fragment 07.0 x 05.5 cm (Box 20, Item P.NYU inv 0798)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0799, cuid31620; 1 fragment 07.5 x 09.0 cm (Box 20, Item P.NYU inv 0799)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0800, cuid31621; 1 fragment 04.5 x 06.0 cm (Box 20, Item P.NYU inv 0800)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0801, cuid31622; 1 fragment 03.5 x 03.0 cm (Box 20, Item P.NYU inv 0801)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0802.01, cuid31623; 1 fragment 02.5 x 03.5 cm (Box 20, Item P.NYU inv 0802.01)